

ZILIN JIN (FULL STACK DEVELOPER)

Shenyang, Liaoning, China 86 155 4157 4099 timon0305@outlook.com www.linkedin.com/in/timon0305

Having developed applications in a multitude of environments from business, to engineering and manufacturing disciplines. Enjoying the challenge of solving problems of all types as well as simply automating manual processes. Software and technology manager with over 6 years of experiences in software development project implementation, intensive knowledge on application development and relevant experience in Software Development Life Cycles (SDLC)

EXPERIENCE

DECEMBER 2021 – APRIL 2022 BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

SIGNED TRADE

Signed is a digital marketplace where musicians list their own crypto tokens backed by music royalties. The more people streaming a musician, the higher their token's value. Support and Invest in your favorite musician, while your pockets grow with them.

Supply and Demand is a big factor that determines the value of anything that can be traded, including all digital currencies in the market. For example, if more people are trying to buy a musician's token, while others are willing to sell them, the price will go up and vice versa. And since the supply of all tokens are limited, the increased popularity will drive up prices as a musician gains more social clout. Each tokens is also pumped out every times a musician's royalty pay, driving up the value of said token.

FEBRARY 2022 – APRIL 2022 MOBILE DEVELOPER

SOCIAL SOLUTIONS

Social Solutions is the leading provider of cloud software for nonprofit and public sector social service organizations, It was recently announced that Social Solutions is combining with Every Action and Cyber Grants to create the second-largest and fastest-growing social good software company in the world

JULY 2021 – DECEMBER 2021 REACT DEVELOPER

TISKARSKA 10 108 00 PRAGUE CZECH REPUBLIC

Assisted with payroll and Pensions service management for 150+ employees. Prepared invoices for more than 200 clients. Assisted with bill payments, records organization and preparation, and other office duties to support financial and accounting operations.

AUGUST 2020 – AUGUST 2021 FULL STACK DEVELOPEPR

CIGNA HEALTHCARE

With \$0 virtual care (telehealth),1 \$0 preventive care visits,2 and \$3 or less for generic prescription drugs,3 Cigna's plans and programs make it easy for you to get affordable, quality care.

Connect with virtual care doctors and nurses, or customer service, when you need them. Have a critical health situation? Get dedicated support with the My Personal Champion® program, making it easier to navigate the health care system.

The myCigna website and mobile app4 help you find quality in-network providers, order and refill prescriptions, pay claims, and more. You also get data-driven customized alerts for health coaching, specialized care, and cost savings—all based on your unique heath care needs.

AUGUST 2018 – MARCH 2020 FULL STACK DEVELOPEPR

DAPP AYAN

This Dap-ayan system formed part of the cultural practices by various towns in Ilocos Norte; however, as political structures became more formal, the use of Dap-ayan has been reduced. In the past, some people have been considering the Dap-ayan as chatting [pagtutungtungan] or drinking [paggi-inuman] place and other user were not noticed.

SEPTEMBER 2017 – DECEMBER 2018 PROGRAMMER

II FAN

iLearn is SFSU's learning management system, where instructors can organize their courses and materials and students can efficiently interact with resources and participate in classes. iLearn is built on the Moodle platform with some local customizations to fit University guidelines and user requests.

EDUCATION

AUGUST 2017

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE, THE HONGKONG UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

- Online Course
- Applying to company as Intern
- Interview

SKILLS

- PHP (HTML, Core PHP, Laravel, CodeIgniter, WordPress, Shopify, Drupal, Symfony)
- JavaScript (React, Redux, Next, Angular, Vue, Vuetify, Nest, Node, Express)
- Python (Flask, Django, ML)
- Java (Spring Boot), C# (Asp.net, .Net Core)
- Version Control (Github, Gitlab, Bitbucket)
- QA (Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes, CI/CD)
- Database (MySQL, MongoDB, OracleDB)
- AWS, Microservices

ACTIVITIES & INTERESTS

- Football
- Body Building
- Running

- Reading
- Skiing
- Travel